

054-2609225 itzikil@icloud.com

Full-stack Developer https://github.com/ltzikil

Summary

Full-Stack Web Developer with experience in writing single-page-applications using the latest WEB technologies (Vue.js, Vuex, Node.js, React.js, Redux, Angular, etc.).

Graduate of the Coding Academy - 640 hours of an intensive coding bootcamp that qualifies Full-Stack developers.

My latest work: Fiverr clone (Vue.js, Node.js, MongoDB):

https://gigerr.onrender.com/

Tech skills

- MVC Frameworks, Single Page Applications and PWA using Vue.js, React and Angular.
- Server-side programming, APIs and REST with Node.js.
- Modern JavaScript (ES6) including Object Oriented Programing.
- HTML5, CSS3 and SASS.
- MongoDB.
- Very basic knowledge at php, jQuery, MySQL.
- Other tech I like to use Tailwind, Boostrap, Vite, Express, Git.

Professional Experience

2021-2022	Music teacher - Groups and private lessons
2018-2021	Backliner - Building and operating stages at music concerts
2018-2021	Volunteering with Impact scholarship - Food distribution
2015-2017	Army service - Command post of battalion commander at Givati

Education

2022-2023	Full-Stack Web Coding Bootcamp, Coding Academy
2018-2022	Music school, Mizmor
2012-2018	Yeshiva, Itamar

Other Interests Sports, music, new technologies.

Qualities Autodidact, self-discipline, curiosity, perceptive.

Other Programs Cubase and DaVinci Resolve.

Languages Hebrew - mother-tongue, English - fluent.